# Set 3 Audit Report: Flagged Questions

Found 213 flagged questions requiring manual review.

### Flagged Question 1
**Reasons:** Keyword match: more than one defensible answer
**Cadre:** BScN | **Paper:** Paper I | **Unit:** Medical-Surgical Nursing
**Question:** One of the following true about stomas:
- A. Healthy stomas are grey, bleed on touch, sensation on touch
- B. Colostomy bag should be emptied when full.
- C. Healthy stomas are pink, bleed on touch, has sensation on touch.
- D. It is yellow, bleeds on touch, there is no sensation on touch.
**Keyed Answer:** C
**Rationale:** A healthy stoma is pink/red and moist, and slightly bleeds on touch because it is vascular. Note the stoma mucosa itself has no pain sensation; option C is the closest/best correct description among the choices (Brunner & Suddarth's Medical-Surgical Nursing).
âš  More than one defensible answer

---

### Flagged Question 2
**Reasons:** Keyword match: more than one defensible answer
